▍2026 辛辛那提 ATP1000 第三轮
德米纳尔 7-5 7-6(3) 弗雷 · 赛后场上采访
Alex big congratulations that was not easy
恭喜你 亚历克斯 这真不容易
with the rain delay you had the momentum
雨断之前你本来占着主动
but you had to fight hard in the end
但最后关头拼得很艰难
and dig deep how would you able
你是怎么咬牙坚持下来
to pull another tie breakout
又拼下一个抢七
in a challenging match?
打完这么胶着的一场球？
Yeah look obviously you never really want
是啊 说实话谁都不想
to go into rain delay being 5 -1 up I think
在五比一领先时碰上雨断
it's it was a tough day there was five
那天真的很难熬 前后大概
or six rain delays I can't remember a match
停了五六次雨 我想不起
that I've had where there's
还有哪场球
been so many starts and stops
这样反反复复地停过
but I'm happy with the way I found
但我很高兴 最终
a way I mean again it got it got tough
找到了办法 到最后确实
at the end probably a little bit harder than it
变得比原本
should have been but I dug deep I got
更难打了 但我咬牙坚持
through and I'm excited
拿下了 我很期待
to be in the next round.
接下来这一轮
I like what you said
我很喜欢你说过的一句话
after a previous match too those challenges
上一场赛后你也说过 这种考验
can be so rewarding what positive outlook
其实很有价值 从中
can you take from getting through this one
你能带来什么正面收获
as well?
呢？
Yeah exactly that I mean it
是啊 没错 我是说
was a very tough match from from start
这场球从头到尾
to finish I think you know I played
都很艰难 我觉得前面
a very very good match until that kind
打得非常非常好 直到
of last rain delay right and then then
最后那次雨断 之后
at the end I had to dig deep I had to kind
我不得不咬牙坚持
of reset just take it a point by at a time
重新调整 一分一分地打
and I managed to dig a big kind
又拼下了一个
of tiebreak again like I
关键的抢七 就像
did in that first round match
我首轮那场一样
so look I'm taking positives
所以我在往好处想
and I'm taking a lot of confidence out
从这些艰难的胜利里
of these types of tough wins and you
积累了不少信心
know hopefully every day I feel better
希望自己一天比一天
and I play better.
感觉更好 打得更好
Fantastic way to get through good job.
赢得漂亮 干得好
Thank you.
谢谢